ntsforums.com 2016-04-06

# Privacy Policy - NTS | National Testing Service

NTS is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, your first and last name, your home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home.

However, you may choose to allow us for delivery of information to third parties if you wish to do so by ticking the appropriate box in your Online Registration Form or by any other means you may find convenient, and that it is verifiable by NTS that you have done so.

This would imply that you as a candidate hereby consent to processing of information about Candidate by NTS and associated companies in connection with the operation of the Program, the Exam(s) and test you have or wish to take. Such processing may include disclosure to third parties, such as your employer and disclosure to or within NTS or its associated organizations and institutions. Such processing may include transfer of information outside Pakistan.

Candidate shall be responsible to ensure that such information is accurate and current. NTS shall have no responsibility for incorrect information provided by NTS to third parties in response to a proper request by a third party to verify a test. The above conditions are valid for one or more tests or any correspondence between you and NTS in any form.

**Disclaimer:** This is not the official website of National Testing Service of Pakistan. This is a non-commercial website helping individuals who intend to join National Testing Service of Pakistan. The material on this website is provided for informational purposes only. We do not claim that the site is an exhaustive compilation of information about National Testing Service of Pakistan neither represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability of any information, content contained on, or linked, downloaded or accessed from any page of this website. These materials are intended, but not promised or guaranteed to be current, complete or up to date. However, honest efforts have been made to provide comprehensive information for the benefit of users. The documents and material displayed or mentioned on this site are not official copies. Please contact NTS for updated rules and regulations governing NTS examination. [Google+](https://plus.google.com/108073753948854522253)

  1.  
  2. [Privacy Policy](http://www.ntsforums.com/privacypolicy/)
  3. [FAQ's ](http://www.ntsforums.com/index.php?app=forums&module=extras&section=boardrules "FAQ") · 
  4. Shorten URL
